psxhax.com 2019-05-26

# Privacy policy | PSXHAX - PSXHACKS

**» Privacy Policy**

Latest Update: 8 May 2018 

We are PSXHAX - PSXHACKS ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information please contact us. 

PSXHAX.COM is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online. 

**» What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers PSXHAX.COM's treatment of personally identifiable information that PSXHAX.COM collects when you are on the PSXHAX.COM site, and when you use PSXHAX.COM services. This policy also covers PSXHAX.COM's treatment of any personally identifiable information that PSXHAX.COM's partners share with PSXHAX.COM. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that PSXHAX.COM does not own or control, or to people that PSXHAX.COM does not employ or manage. 

**» Information Collection and Use**

PSXHAX.COM collects personally identifiable information when you register for a PSXHAX.COM account and when you use certain PSXHAX.COM services. PSXHAX.COM may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. When you register with PSXHAX.COM, we ask for several details which may or may not include your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Eventhough you register with PSXHAX.COM and sign in to our services, you are still anonymous to us. PSXHAX.COM also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, PSXHAX.COM cookie information and the page you requested. This information is used only for internal purposes by PSXHAX.COM technical support Staff. PSXHAX.COM uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. 

**» What information we hold about you**

The type of data that we collect and process includes: 

  * Your name or username.
  * Your email address.
  * Your IP address.

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

  * You register as a member on this site.
  * You fill out our contact form.
  * You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
  * You fill out fields on your profile.

**» How your personal information is used**

We may use your personal information in the following ways: 

  * For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
  * We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
  * Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

**» Other ways we may use your personal information.**

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails in your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

**» Information Sharing and Disclosure**

It is policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you may provide us, such as through our forum, chat or by email used only for the purposes for which you provide the information. For example, if you choose to give your name and/or any other personal information it is completely by your own will. PSXHAX.COM will not solicit or provide any private information to outside vendors or organizations. Information you choose to submit on our site is for public view and at your discretion. Therefore any information you submit publicly on PSXHAX.COM by way of forums or chats can be viewed by outside sources. Any emails submitted to any member of PSXHAX.COM will remain privately held and no such information will be made public unless user permission is granted. PSXHAX.COM will ONLY send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

We have your consent to share the information;  
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process. 

**» Cookies**

PSXHAX.COM may set and access PSXHAX.COM cookies on your computer. PSXHAX.COM allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to PSXHAX.COM's cookies. 

**» Cookie policy**

Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on this page.

**» Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

**» Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences**

PSXHAX.COM gives you the ability to edit your PSXHAX.COM Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want PSXHAX.COM to contact you. 

**» Interest-based Advertising**

DoubleClick DART cookie FAQ: http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx 

\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on PSXHAX.COM.  
\- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy (http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see here: http://www.networkadvertising.org 

**» DoubleClick Privacy Disclosure**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. The third-party advertising technology that we use on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. To "opt-out," please visit here: http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx. 

**» Exponential Interactive, Inc Privacy Disclosure**

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com). 

**» Security**

Your PSXHAX.COM Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. 

**» Keeping your data secure**

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

**» Acceptance of this policy**

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we may further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

**» Changes to this Privacy Policy**

PSXHAX.COM may amend this policy from time to time without prior warning. Please check frequently for the latest version. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future. 

PSXHAX.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of any affiliates or 3rd party organizations displayed within our Web site. 

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us via the link below: 

<https://www.psxhax.com/misc/contact>
